https://magritek.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentSpinsolve 80 MHzDiscover the newest member of the Spinsolve family.
show more
Spinsolve 80 MHzDiscover the newest member of the Spinsolve family.
show more
AutosamplerIncrease your sample measurements throughput by integrating the new autosampler with your Spinsolve
show more
AutosamplerIncrease your sample measurements throughput by integrating the new autosampler with your Spinsolve
show more
Reaction MonitoringThe Spinsolve high-resolution benchtop NMR spectrometer can be installed directly in the fume hood of a chemistry lab to monitor the progress of chemical reactions on-line.
show more
Reaction MonitoringThe Spinsolve high-resolution benchtop NMR spectrometer can be installed directly in the fume hood of a chemistry lab to monitor the progress of chemical reactions on-line.
show more
Spinsolve ULTRAThe homogeneity of a superconducting magnet on your bench
show more
Spinsolve ULTRAThe homogeneity of a superconducting magnet on your bench
show more
Home
About us
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyYour privacy is important to usWe respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal data. This policy provides information on how we collect and process your personal data through your use of the Magritek website, including any data you may provide us when you request to be contacted, buy something from us, request a quote, sign up for a newsletter or interact in other ways with our website and company. From time to time we may update our Privacy Policy by updating this webpage.What information do we collect?When you use our website, fill out a form, send us an email, or otherwise interact with our company we collect, retain and update the personal information you provided to us. This information may include your name, email address, phone number, the company you work for and their mailing address, product/service interests and preferences or other details provided to us at the time. How do we use the information we collect?We use the information you provide in the following ways:To enable us to meet our contractual obligations if you buy something from us, such as sending information regarding your order or related services.To allow us to better respond to your customer service requests.To send you the content, related product information, services and offerings which you are most likely to be interested in.To help improve our website in order to enhance your experience.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.We will never sell or pass your personal information to third parties not related to our business, products or services.You will only be contacted by Magritek to inform you about products, services or other matters related to your relationship with Magritek.The basis for processing your information is either with respect to a contract we have with you, for our legitimate business interests (taking into account any potential impact on you both positive and negative), or for us to comply with the law.We use a number of cloud-based software services to administer and run our business. Some of your personal information may be stored in these systems. We only use services that respect your privacy and that do not allow your information to be shared with other users of those services. We will only send your personal information to third parties where it necessary for us to perform the service with respect to your business interests, such as passing a quote request to one of our distributors who is located in the country you are located in. If you have any specific questions about our use of your personal information not answered here, please contact us at CookiesOur website uses cookies, which are small files that a site transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow it). Cookies enable our website to recognise your browser, capture and remember certain information and respond to you as an individual. You can set your browser to refuse all or some cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies.We use cookies in conjunction with Google Analytics to aggregate data about website interactions to help us improve our service. We have configured Google Analytics to anonymize IP addresses so that no personal information is captured or shared with Google.We also use cookies to record information about your site visit so we can improve your experience by delivering more relevant and personalised information. When you first visit our website you have the choice to accept or refuse these cookies.We use Google AdWords as a third party vendor for marketing purposes, this allows our advertisements to be displayed on other websites, including ones you visit. As well as using your browser to refuse cookies, you can also opt-out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ad Settings.MarketingYou will receive marketing communications from us if you have purchased goods or services from us, provided us with your details when you entered a competition, filled out a website form, or registered for a promotion and you have not opted out of receiving these communications.All marketing emails we send include an opt-out link in the footer. You can use this link at any time to adjust your marketing preferences and to opt-out of receiving any future marketing communications. You can also contact us at
at any time to update your preferences.When you opt-out of receiving marketing communications, we may still use your personal data to communicate with you in regards a product/service purchase, warranty registration or enquiry, product/service experience or in relation to financial transactions.Links to Other WebsitesThe Magritek Website may contain links to third party sites or other online services. We are not responsible for the information and privacy practices of these third parties, as they are subject to their own policies and procedures.Data retentionWe will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.MonitoringWe may monitor and record communications with you for the purpose of quality assurance, training, fraud prevention and compliance.Your rightsPursuant to the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993, you have the right to access, and to request correction to, any of your personal information provided to Magritek. Under the GDPR regulations in the EU you have rights in relation to your personal data including;Request access to your personal data to check its lawful processing;Request correction of your personal data to correct any incomplete or inaccurate data;Request erasure of your personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it;Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format.If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, or you have any other enquiry about your personal information, please contact us at
or send postal mail to Magritek, 6 Hurring Place, Unit 3, Newlands, Wellington 6037, New Zealand, Attention: Privacy.We try to respond to all legitimate requests within 30 days. We may need to confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data as a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.If you have any questions or concerns at all about your privacy or anything in this document, please email us at
or get in touch with us via one of our offices listed on www.magritek.com/contact-usQuestions about our products?Get in touch with us anytime!Call us:Germany: +49 241 9278 7270USA: +1 855 667 6835New Zealand: +64 4 477 7096Drop an email:sales: Support: Quick finderSpinsolve familySpinsolve addonsSpectra Librarypdf repositoryTestimonialsPublicationsBlogVideosAbout usBackgroundOur PeopleDistributorsCareersIntellectual PropertyPrivacy PolicySoftware LicenseDisclaimerApplicationsChemistry EducationReaction MonitoringPolymersForensic Drug AnalysisAnalytical NMRFoodPetrochemicalNMR ResearchResourcesSpectra Librarypdf repositoryTestimonialsPublicationsVideosFAQScienceLinks
